<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<root>
	<home>
		<label>
			Mind is a new way to develop systems
		</label>
		<label>
			From a extremely simple code, based on a semi-natural language, Mind is able to generate a complete system, including its database, classes, forms, documentation, etc.
		</label>
		<label>
			Try this example
		</label>
		<label>
			All the student have many teacher.
		</label>
		<label>
			And each teacher has one or many student.
		</label>
		<label>
			we also know that studend has a name:char(60, needed).
		</label>
		<label>
			Every teacher has a name:character(60, not null) too.
		</label>
		<label>
			we might consider: every student has a mother.
		</label>
		<label>
			With only those simple lines of WML(Web Mind Language) code, Mind 2.0 will give you these outputs (as default, once you can add more by using plugins or different modules):
		</label>
		<label>
			Mind 2.0 will normalize the database implementing all the rules and preparing everything that can my done for a machine, letting you free to use YOUR mind, your creativity to inovate the world, as machines cannot do (yet).
		</label>
		<label>
			Maximum Abstraction
		</label>
		<label>
			TheWebMind will abstract the dataBase, patterns implemention, use of any framework you are used to as much as it has a module to work with, views, documentation, normalization and even the programming language the generated system will be born in. 
			More details and possibilities can be adopted by modules and plugins that you can build by yourself and sell or contribute with the comunity.
		</label>
		<label>
			A discrete programming language
		</label>
		<label>
			The discrete programming language adapts to the developer. We can improve it due to reach a better efficiency from developers in addition to offer support o code in many different languages. Language which you can colaborate too, developing and translating.
		</label>
		<label>
			Sponsors
		</label>
		<label>
			Contribute
		</label>
	</home>
	<footer>
		<label>
			Home
		</label>
		<label>
			Download
		</label>
		<label>
			Docs
		</label>
		<label>
			Videos
		</label>
		<label>
			Contact
		</label>
	</footer>
	<download>
		<label>
			Requirements
		</label>
		<label>
			TheWebMind is an application developed totally  in PHP. You must have a simple HTTP server with PHP support to unzip Mind files and access them using a modern browser.
		</label>
		<label>
			TheWebMind will keep itself up to date as new features or bg fixies are established. You may cnfigure the way Mind deal with updates.
		</label>
		<label>
			Contribute
		</label>
		<label>
			Here, some links to download options of these required elements.
		</label>
		<label>
			Instructions, FAQ and suggestions at:
		</label>
	</download>
	<contact>
		<label>
			Contact
		</label>
		<label>
			Questions? Have you already tried to solve them reading our
		</label>
		<label>
			Want to contribute? Great! Then, subscribe at 
		</label>
		<label>
			Other reason to talk to us?<br/>
			No problems, send us a message usting the following form, join our 
		</label>
		<label>
			Name
		</label>
		<label>
			E-mail
		</label>
		<label>
			Country
		</label>
		<label>
			State
		</label>
		<label>
			City
		</label>
		<label>
			How you reached Mind?
		</label>
		<label>
			Search engines
		</label>
		<label>
			Twitter
		</label>
		<label>
			Discussion groups
		</label>
		<label>
			Announce or indication from a trusty source
		</label>
		<label>
			Different ways
		</label>
		<label>
			Send
		</label>
		<label>
			or 
		</label>
		<label>
			discussion group 
		</label>
		<label>
			or follow us on  
		</label>
	</contact>
	<download_latest>
		<label>
			Your download will start in a few seconds. If it does not happen, please click here: 
		</label>
		<label>
			Thank you for downloading theWebMind
		</label>
		<label>
			Please, provide us your feedback. In case of any difficulties, visit our documentation at:
		</label>
	</download_latest>
</root>